[Music]
what's up guys what's going on what's
happening have you been
welcome to 2021 today i've got
a simplistic system for you guys to be
able to use
going forward for your ceremonies and
let me tell you
i've seen a lot of reviews on this but i
want to give you the most
simplest review that i can possibly give
you
because once i figured out why i needed
this system
i could justify how much the system cost
so let's break down the maui 5
go so one of the things that i started
off with this system looking at is how
compact and everything it is
now i saw that you could actually get
this thing in different colors you can
get it in
different sizes different models things
like that the reason that i actually
picked it
is because it can actually be fully
wireless setup at first i saw that they
had a pa system
didn't quite know the difference between
them or why one was
a couple hundred dollars cheaper but
then i realized it's because
it's not a wireless system it's strictly
still by cord
and you know that we get in situations
where we don't always have
the ability to have a power cord hence
the fact why we need something portable
and wireless so now this setup here is
really really easy to put together it's
really only
three maybe two parts at the most but
you can have some additional accessories
which i have on here for you
so that you can see so the first thing
we'll go over here is actually going to
be
your subwoofer now this is a eight inch
woofer
that you can use here that actually has
some pretty good depth to it i've
actually tested it out on several events
as far as just having ceremony music and
it's more than enough
than you'll ever need for any type of
setup as you can see what i'm showing
here
you can see all the diodes and
everything on the top of them you've got
your
mp3 input bluetooth setup you got your
phone input you got a guitar
a microphone you've got your regular
line in as well as
on the back you also have your xlr left
and right inputs as well as one output
on the back
that you can use as well so the real
magic to this system actually comes in
this little hole right here
imagine this just being your subwoofer
and the way that it makes that this
system go and lets you know that it has
power
is based on these guys so these guys
each serve a purpose believe it or not
each one is different in its own
so the first one that i want to show you
here looks like it may just be a basic
part of the actual setup
however this is probably the most
important part
to make this system actually work on the
back of this guy it has
some leds on the back to let you know
that this is
your battery so this right here is what
how long your system is actually going
to last it has led
lights and stuff on the back to let you
know how much battery you actually have
going forward
so you can actually test the unit just
like so
to see how much battery you have going
out to an event and it
is the first connection that goes right
here so once that's set up
you're now telling the subwoofer that
you have power this is your power
this now becomes a unit that you could
use you can turn it on right now and
fire it right up
this stick right here is just a hollow
stick and listen
you can actually kind of tell and the
weight is a lot different on this one
there's nothing on the back of this one
it's plain
because this is just a stick to get your
speakers up higher
so basically what you do is you plug in
your battery pack first
and then you connect this stick in
between
it connects like so
and then you take your speaker stick
here
and you stick it right at the top and
now you've got a full out system
so here is your battery here's the dummy
stick to raise it up
and here is your speakers now the
speakers actually have
four speakers up at the top and trust me
guys this is
more than enough to be able to get
sound through your ceremony now i've
used this a couple of times and the most
of the people that i've used it on for
an outside event has been 200 people so
this will definitely cover 200 people
worth of sound and i was at the back of
the ceremony when i did that
gentlemen we're going to show you here
that we are now using
the maui 5 go set up here to do the
ceremony and this is going to cover
about 200 people and as you can hear
it's already playing and everything
right now and it's very clear i've had
them check
over there in that corner for whether or
not they can hear
the music clear and they actually told
me to turn it down so now let's take a
look and see what the height is now i'm
six
two and i want to put this together so
you guys can see
about how tall this guy is all right so
let's take all three poles
set them down
and you can see it's past me so this
thing gets a lot of height and stuff on
it i'd probably say it's about the
equivalent of somebody who is six five
maybe even six six and like i said this
produces a
ample amount of sound
[Music]
and that's just coming from my phone so
basically how i set this guy up
is i connected bluetooth to my ipad that
i've already pre-done the music for the
ceremony in
and then i just hit play and let it just
do its thing now one thing i want to say
about this guy is it is great
for just music what i have learned over
doing multiple gigs
is that this guy may need an additional
mixer
just to get volume for your lapels now
for a wireless mic
it's been great it does fantastic but if
you guys want to use a lapel with it
i've actually had to turn the microphone
port
all the way up to all the way as far as
it will go
in order for it to get sound through the
speakers that are
loud enough to be able to cover a bigger
crowd so if you only got like
maybe 25 to 75 which most of these
weddings are with everything that's
going on
then you'll be okay but to cover 200
people you definitely want to get that
that clear crisp sound and plus it
doesn't have any feedback that comes
with it i can stand
right in front of this guy and there not
be any problem with feedback when it
comes to
a microphone even a lapel now like i
said it's easy to set this guy up
look how fast i did it at this event
and then here you can see how i have it
set up with a wireless lapel
all right so here we go right here
outside and we're going to show you the
quick setup here
[Music]
we have got the maui 5 go all set up we
only got one wire that's coming from the
lapel
into the maui 5 go
and the battery charger or the battery
pack is the thing that's charging this
here
so i got it all set up here i'm out of
the way and as soon as the ceremony and
everything's done i'll take it right
back inside
and so like i said that's why i know
that i needed an additional mixer
in order to make this guy run with the
wireless lapel if i needed to cover a
larger crowd now
for my smaller crowds though i'm not
always going to bring this i like to
switch it up and stuff sometimes this
helps me out when i'm out in a field or
out on an
air open area this was perfect for a
couple of events that i've already done
last year so going into this year when
the bride gives me her
venue i would definitely double check
and see what where they're having the
ceremony
and everything at and use it for that
this can also be a great tool if you're
having a mixer or if you're having a
cocktail hour right after the ceremony
this is great to pop up in a corner you
can play soft jazz music or whatever
music that the bride and groom actually
wanted for their cocktail hour
and it's perfect you never have to worry
about the quality of sound with this guy
now i know a couple of you guys are
probably asking well jay why do you have
four sticks on here if it only needs
three well what i did was i made sure
that i had enough batteries so if i
forget to charge one
at least i have another one to have
charged which it has not happened yet
because
these guys run off of a great battery
i've run this thing
probably on three gigs in the row three
ceremonies in a row
and we're talking about about an hour's
worth of play each time so
about three hours and it's barely lost
any charge so i'm assuming it's probably
about anywhere from five to seven
hours worth of continuous play for each
one of the batteries
and a great accessory and everything
that it has as well
is these bags now these bags are great
because this helps take care of your
equipment so i'll go from right to left
here
and show you this bag
this bag actually covers up your
subwoofer it goes right over the top
has a handle and everything in the back
for you to be able to carry it
only thing it doesn't cover is the
bottom and you can see that's wide open
there
then you've got this back here that has
four different ports and everything
inside of it holds four different sticks
so you can take them
[Music]
pop them all in
and then take the top close it
[Music]
and now it's ready to be carried it's
just that portable this is what i'm
going to be using going forth into the
wedding season i'm not going to forget
about the bose s1 because i'm going to
use it for the smaller events
but if i have to run cocktail and i have
to run ceremony
and it's a bigger crowd i'm probably
going to be using the maui 5 go
wireless because it just makes total
sense you guys leave me some comments
and everything down below let me know
what you think
about the unit whether or not it would
help you out whether or not you've
already looked into it i'm sure
a lot of you guys already have this
system but i just wanted to show you
because i like to show you guys the gear
and stuff that i use
at these events i'll leave links below
for all the gear and everything that
i've showed you and stuff here
we've got more coming for 2021 if you
can do me a favor before you get out of
here make sure you hit that thumbs up
button for me
as well as subscribe to the channel and
turn on those post notifications so that
you can be notified when i put out
another video
let's get into 2021 guys and let's start
it off with a bang
this guy will see you soon so will i and
if you don't know
now you know peace people
you